<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Advaya</string>
    <string name="advaya">Have we ever seen a young Michael Jackson dance to the tunes or have we ever heard Shreya Ghosal croon in her teens? Did anyone of us have an opportunity to witness Picasso draw a masterpiece?  Or have we watched the early short films of Martin Scorsese?  Have any of us been in midst of an audience full of beans every second? Even if so, could we experience all of these in one place? Yes!! All these utopian events took form on 27th of august at the cultural event of PSGiTech – Advaya !!The word Advaya means unique and the students of PSGitech proved that the event was named right. The event kicked off with a semi classical dance which mesmerized the audience. The Tamil debate competition set the agenda for the day – shear display of talent!  These were followed by the voguish and trendy events like Connexions, Pattuku pattu, Oru sol Oru varthai where the students displayed their skill and knowledge across diversified domains.  The Argumentative Indian in the students was seen clearly with fiery English debates on various topics.  The Mime show was the highlight of the event which conveyed subtle and delicate messages on ragging, jallikattu etc in great manner. They clearly proved that actions speak louder than a trillion words.Though the scorching sun’s might died down in the evening, the performance of the students remained robust.  The Itech Band which started the art show for the day gave numerous performances which enthralled the audience. The singers with their lively performance lit up the evening. The mimicry show that followed up created a laughing riot. The students emulated the voice of famous personalities  along with their style that left us in awe. The dancers came into the fore after this and  took the centre stage. Their wondrous moves had us all transfixed to the stage and shout out showing our admiration.  The event concluded with a short film directed and acted by the students of Itech which bubbled with creativity.All through the week before the cultural day, students have been participating in various events that extended into the night. Nothing seemed to deter their spirit as they participated in numbers. Miraculous performances seemed to unfold each and every second on the final day. All these was plausible due to  the extreme ebullience of the audience. Their applause for all the performances raised the roof which helped the students compete with vigour.In toto, this will be  an event  that will be remembered for the quality it has produced and it will  always be a preferred day for the students to walk down the memory lane!! </string>
</resources>
